{
    "id": "72ad0806cbf4442294688b22010729a4",
    "title": "Passive Voice Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "My pen ………………………….. stolen.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "has been",
                "is being"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………………………. invited to the party.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have",
                "have been",
                "am being"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "English ………………………………. all over the world.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "speaks",
                "spoken",
                "is spoken"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He ……………………………… admittance by the guard.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "refused",
                "has refused",
                "was refused"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The captive ……………………………………. to a tree.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "bound",
                "has bound",
                "was bound"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "All orders ………………………………. promptly.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "execute",
                "will execute",
                "will be executed"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The letter ……………………………. posted.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "has been",
                "been"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The horse …………………………….. frightened by the noise.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "was",
                "has been"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The exhibition ……………………………… by the Chief Minister.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "inaugurated",
                "has inaugurated",
                "was inaugurated"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The theatre ……………………………. only last month.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "opened",
                "has opened",
                "was opened"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}